She did it. And boy, is she sorry.
Sibling Rivalry is a comedy, romance film directed by Carl Reiner.
Marjorie Turner is suffocating in her marriage and day to day life.
An extramarital affair with a stranger seems to be the answer until her paramour has a fatal
heart attack, and turns out to be less of a stranger than she could have thought...
Marjorie Turner, played by Kirstie Alley.
Nicholas Meany, played by Bill Pullman.
Iris Turner-Hunter, played by Carrie Fisher.
Jeanine, played by Jami Gertz.
Harry Turner, played by Scott Bakula.
Rose Turner, played by Frances Sternhagen.
Sibling Rivalry is a 1990 American black comedy film directed by Carl Reiner and starring Kirstie
Alley, Sam Elliott, Jami Gertz, Bill Pullman, Carrie Fisher, and Scott Bakula.
The film explores themes of hotel room, police,
salesman, sibling rivalry, extramarital affair.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.